(Sheldon:)I see you bought Mama Italia
marinara spaghetti sauce.
(Penny:)-Yep.
-That's the sauce my mother uses.
(Sheldon:)She likes cooking Italian...
(Sheldon:)...because, according to her,
that's what the Romans made Jesus eat.
(Penny:)Interesting. I'll have to have you over
for spaghetti some night.
(Sheldon:)I'm hungry now.
(Penny:)Oh, um, okay. Why don't you give me
an hour and come over?
(Sheldon:)Will you cut up hot dogs into little
chunks and mix them in with the sauce?
(Penny:)-I don't have hot dogs.
-It's all right. I do.
Oh. You're in for what my mother calls
a real Italian treat.
(Leonard:)-Hey, where you been?
-I was talking with Penny.
(Howard:)What's wrong with you? You can't
hang out with your roommate's ex.
(Howard:)That's totally uncool.
(Leonard:)No, it's fine. I don't care. I'm over it.
Yeah. That's why he's been whining...
(Raj:)...about trying to invent that
memory-wiper gizmo from Men in Black.
(Sheldon:)Is he making any progress?